<?xml version="1.0"?>
<exercise xmlns:msxml="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:util="urn:nxlevel-com:util">
  <tab1 label="Scenario" image="images/m01_s06_t08.png">
    <instruction><![CDATA[<p>Cheryl is a lab chemist and requires samples for a research project right away. She finds a vendor in China that can send her the samples she needs. However, the vendor states there will be a 20% premium on the shipment.</p>
<p>What are some questions Cheryl needs to answer before deciding to order the samples from this vendor?</p>]]></instruction>
    <instruction><![CDATA[<i>Select the <b>Course of Action</b> tab to enter your answers.</i>]]></instruction>
  </tab1>
  <tab2 label="Response">
    <instruction><![CDATA[<p><i>What are some questions Cheryl needs to answer before deciding to order the samples from this vendor?</i></p><p><i>Select all that apply. When you are satisfied with your choices, select <b>Submit</b>.</i></p>]]></instruction>
    <instruction><![CDATA[<i>Select the <b>Case Study</b> tab if you want to review the case study.</i>]]></instruction>
       <choice correct="0">
      <text><![CDATA[Can the premium be charged to a subsidiary company located in China?]]></text>
    </choice>
    <choice correct="1">
      <text><![CDATA[Is the vendor wholly or in part owned by the government?]]></text>
    </choice>
    <choice correct="1">
      <text><![CDATA[Has this vendor been previously vetted by the company?]]></text>
    </choice>
	    <choice correct="1">
      <text><![CDATA[Is the premium charge for the shipment normal or unique to this vendor?]]></text>
    </choice>
	    <choice correct="0">
      <text><![CDATA[Can she pay for the premium with a credit card instead of being invoiced?]]></text>
    </choice>
    
    <feedbackCorrect><![CDATA[<p>Correct! Before moving forward Cheryl needs to know whether the vendor is in any way owned by the government to determine if the individuals with whom she deals could be considered government officials – although commercial bribery still presents a risk under the U.K. Bribery Act. Cheryl must also determine if the vendor has been vetted for compliance risks by her company in the past. Using an un-vetted vendor could prove to be a compliance risk. She must also determine if the premium is normal for similar vendors shipping orders under the same circumstances, or if this is a unique charge for this particular vendor. If the charge is unique to this vendor, or excessive compared to other vendors, it is a corruption red flag. <i>Select <b>Close</b> to continue.</i></p>]]></feedbackCorrect>
    <feedbackIncorrect><![CDATA[<p>Incorrect. The correct answers are identified by the green arrows. Cheryl should not have the cost of the shipment charged to a subsidiary located in China, nor should she pay the premium with a credit card instead of being invoiced for it. Cheryl needs to determine if the vendor is owned by the government in order to know if she could be dealing with individuals considered government officials – although commercial bribery still presents a risk under the U.K. Bribery Act. She also needs to know if the vendor has been previously vetted by the company for compliance. Using an un-vetted vendor is a compliance risk. She also needs to determine if the premium is normal for similar vendors shipping orders under the same circumstances, or if this is a unique charge for this particular vendor. If the charge is unique to this vendor, or excessive compared to other vendors, it is a corruption red flag. <i>Select <b>Close</b> to continue.</i></p>]]></feedbackIncorrect>

  </tab2>
</exercise>